Interviewer: Do you go out on Friday night?
Kat: Yes, my husband Eddie and I always go out for a drink or for dinner.
Interviewer: Where do you go?
Kat: We usually go to our local pub, because they have good food there.
We sometimes meet friends there, too.
Interviewer: What time do you get up on Saturday and Sunday?
Kat: On Saturday at seven thirty. On Sunday it depends. At about nine?
Interviewer: What do you usually do on a Saturday?
Kat: I work from nine to four. I’m a hairdresser and we’re open on Saturdays.
Then after work I go to the supermarket and buy food for the week.
In the evening, we usually stay at home and watch TV.
My husband’s a big football fan and he always watches Match of the Day.
Interviewer: Where do you usually have lunch on Sunday?
Kat: With my parents, or sometimes Eddie’s parents.
My dad makes a very good Sunday lunch – he’s the cook in the family.
Interviewer: Are you tired on Sunday evening?
Kat: Yes, because in the afternoon we need to do housework. Cleaning, washing, things like that.
Interviewer: Do you do the same thing every weekend?
Kat: Yeah – more or less. Except when we’re on holiday.
Interviewer: What’s your favourite part of the weekend?
Kat: Friday night, definitely!